Finding Aid for the Clara Hieronymus Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- News Clips Album 5 (Box 19)
- News Clippings packet 1 (Box 20)
- Envelope and letter to Clara (Box 20)
- News Clippings Album (Box 20)
- The Challenge (Box 20)
- Empty folders (Box 20)
- Cheekwood mirror (Box 20)
- Folders/ signs (Box 21)
- Invitation to Clara Hieronymus (Box 21)
- At home (Box 21)
- Clara/photography of Clara (Box 21)
- New York Herald Tribune/ Today’s living (Box 21)
- Random Clara stuff (Box 21)
- The Seven- League sunflower/ script (Box 21)
- Folder writing (Box 21)
- Folder with writing on it (Box 21)
- Another folder with writing on it (Box 21)
- Clara on a talk show/ write-up (Box 21)
- John Wathon Logan (Box 21)
- Catherine the Great Trip early ‘90s (Box 21)
- General correspondence (Box 22)
  some in response to Hieronymus articles
  some articles associated with New York City/ New York Times
- Notes on William Faulkner’s Requiem for a Nun: On Stage & Off (Box 22)
- New York Times misc. & general New York theater articles (Box 22)
- Grant information (Box 22)
- Misc. theater pamphlets & information (Box 23)
- Misc. Hieronymus articles + two letters (Box 23)
- General correspondence (Box 23)
- Random Pamphlets (Box 23)
- Awards & Recognitions (Box 23)
- Random & Photos (Box 23)
- Nashville Opera for the Deaf (Box 24)
- TN Bicentennial Celebration (Box 24)
- London Theater Flight Info (Box 24)
- General Correspondence (Box 24)
  including info about the S. C. Hieronymus Award for accomplishments in Medical Humanities
- Pamphlets (Box 24)
- Articles + magazines (Box 24)
- Random (Box 24)
- May ’95 Photos (Box 25)
- Random/Loose Photos (Box 25)
- 10-22-79 photos + 1980 photos (Box 25)
- 1996 (Box 25)
- Date unknown, but grouped (Box 25)
- Unknown European trip + 1600s Magyar currency (Box 25)
- Forest Hills Info (Box 26)
- Letters from Major’s office – Forest Hills (Box 26)
- Forest Hills Story Idea (Box 26)
- Forest Hills Newsletters (Box 26)
- Forest Hills Election Notes (Box 26)
- Forest Hills city manager letters (Box 26)
- Forest Hills quarterly newsletters (Box 26)
- Forest Hills sheets & residents (Box 26)
- Forest Hills Beautification committee (Box 26)
- Forest Hills Commission (Box 26)
- Forest Hills more story ideas (Box 26)
- Kevin Grogan notes (Box 26)
- Le Petit Salon notes (Box 26)
- Le Petit Salon programs (Box 26)
- Folder of various stuff: Le Petit Salon, correspondence, theater newsletters, etc… (Box 26)
- General Articles (Box 26)
- American Theatre Critics Association, Inc. (Box 26)
- Clara articles and letters to Clara (Box 27)
- Piazza Cosmopolitan Mix (script) (Box 27)
- Play pamphlets (Box 27)
- Corey Everyman (Box 27)
- Accolade to Clara (Box 27)
- Award of Merit (Box 27)
- The Auction Studio (Box 27)
- Miller’s poems to Clara (Box 27)
- More Clara articles on the arts (Box 27)
- Samaritans (Box 27)
- Tennessee Arts Commission (Box 27)
- Annual Manual (Box 27)
- Clara Letters (Box 27)
- Photos (Box 27)
- In the news (Box 27)
- April 26 (Box 27)
- Tennessee honors Clara (Box 27)
- Post cards:, 1986 (Box 27)
- Letters (Box 27)
- More Clara writings in Newspapers (Box 27)
- Performances and programs (Box 27)
- Newsletter (Box 27)
- Alternative Root (Box 27)
- Nov. 21, 1975 Trooping the group: a look at theatre (Box 27)
- Many more scripts (Box 27)
- Talks Clara plus news articles8/8/76 (Box 27)
- Journalism students (Box 27)
- Letters about Clara (Box 27)
- Clara article on ninth graders and theater (Box 27)
- Vanderbilt letter and handwritten remarks (Box 27)
- 1995 news and performance critiques (Box 27)
- Photos (Box 27)
- News and correspondence (Box 28)
- Photos (Box 28)
- In the News (Box 28)
- Rhode Island College Letter (Box 28)
- More correspondence (Box 28)
- Critiques of scripts (Box 28)
- Magazines and pamphlets (Box 28)
- More News clippings (Box 28)
- File with various information with an invitation from Mayor Bill Boner attached (Box 28)
- Letters and newspaper articles (Box 28)
- The University of Georgia (Box 28)
- The University of Tennessee at Nashville (Box 28)
- Various news clippings (Box 28)
- In the News (Box 29)
- Shoe’s on the other feet (Box 29)
- Some (Box 29)
- Fax to Patrick Connelly (Box 29)
- Nashville academics theatre (Box 29)
- NEA talent showcase (Box 29)
- Tributes and performances (Box 29)
- Gala (Box 29)
- Pictures and plays (Box 29)
- Speak easy (Box 29)
- Art and theatre by Clara (Box 29)
- Clara writings (Box 29)
- Shakespeare Plays (Box 29)
- Aristotle’s ethics (Box 29)
- Scripts (Box 29)
- Oct. 9 1967 (Box 29)
- James Joyce (Box 29)
- Book reviews (Box 29)
- Theatre crafts (Box 29)
- Mrs. Clara (Box 30)
- Magazine and Nashville stuff (Box 30)
- Order of props and scripts (Box 30)
- Heart of Juliet Jones (Box 30)
- Samson Agonist (Box 30)
- Handwritten letter and “A look at the best” (Box 30)
- Clara in the news (Box 30)
- Magazine letter and other various stuff (Box 30)
- Naras (National Academy of recording arts) (Box 30)
- Department of art/studio museum (Box 30)
- Up to Shakespeare (Box 30)
- To Clara: letters (Box 30)
- Fisk honors Clara (Box 30)
- 2 Clara Photos (Box 30)
- By Clara (Box 30)
- “good speed” (Box 30)
- Fortinbras gets down (Box 30)
- Powerful god (Box 30)
- The connection by Clara (Box 30)
- Theater criticism (Box 30)
- Clara Hieronymus (Box 30)
- Letter, Belmont College (Box 30)
- News Discards (Box 30)
- Pamphlet (Box 30)
- News, April-June 1992 (Box 30)
- Nashville community (Box 30)
- Doughtry’s pamphlets (Box 30)
- 25 top paying magazines (Box 30)
- Motler Hicks-center stage (Box 30)
- Garden full of love (Box 30)
- Museum of Modern Art (Box 30)
- History Institute (Box 30)
- “man of la mocha” (Box 30)
- Nashville’s angels (Box 30)
- The Nashville’s children theaters (Box 30)
- Backstage (Box 30)
- Christy (Box 30)
- Don’t sensor the naked truth (Box 30)
- The Nashville’s children theater (Box 30)
- Proof of story (Box 30)
- TPAC 95-96 (Box 30)
- The groundhog (Box 30)
- Lee Harvey (Box 30)
- The Opry goes to Broadway (Box 30)
- Furniture Review (Box 30)
- Chaffin (Box 30)
- “center stage” (Box 30)
- The trip to bountiful (Box 30)
- Nashville Children’s Theater (Box 30)
- Proof of story (Box 30)
- TPAC 95-96 (Box 30)
- Center stage (Box 30)
- The trip to bountiful (Box 30)
- Nashville Children’s Theater (Box 30)
- American criticism (Box 31)
- Old Master (Box 31)
- 75TH Birthday (Box 31)
- The Tennessean (Box 31)
- Dear Clara (Box 31)
- 1994 (Box 31)
- Article: “Lets hear it for Clara” (Box 31)
- Sunday Morning (Box 31)
- Better Living articles (Box 31)
- 1976-1977 (Box 31)
- News articles by Clara (Box 31)
- Clara, Tennessean, 1984 (Box 31)
- Various letters and articles (Box 31)
- Confirmation report (Box 31)
- Theatre Review (Box 31)
- Garson (Box 31)
- Better Living (Box 31)
- Henderson Art’s Council (Box 31)
- Parallels (Box 31)
- Terry Tomlin (Box 31)
- The foundation of theatre (Box 31)
- Maya, 1966 (Box 31)
- Narcica Titman (Box 31)
- Cover-to-cover (Box 31)
- 1969 (Box 31)
- Clara Letter (Box 31)
- Commercial (Box 31)
- More Letters (Box 31)
- Joan Root (Box 31)
- Various Clara Info (Box 32)
- Letter: The University Of South Alabama (Box 32)
- Alabama (Box 32)
- Clara in the new (Box 32)
- Photos of Clara (Box 32)
- More photos (Box 32)
- Dear Clara (Box 32)
- Clara Hieronymus (Box 32)
- Letter from Interior Design Institute (Box 32)
- Nashville Children’s Theater (Box 32)
- Shakespeare Association of America (Box 32)
- Color slides (Box 32)
- Of Tree and Tree houses (Box 32)
- On stage October 1st (Box 32)
- The Tennessean, 1977 (Box 33)
- Eagle Sets The Mood (Box 33)
- The Scene/2005 (Box 33)
- HCA pledges 50,000 to Healthhall (Box 33)
- Mitchell House True Collaboration (Box 33)
- Better Living, June 11th (Box 33)
- The Tennessean 1977 part 2 (Box 33)
- The Tennessean 1977 part 3 (Box 33)
- 1974 (Box 33)
- Postcards (one from the Gore Family) (Box 33)
- The Esteemed Clara (Awards) (Box 33)
- Los Angeles Times (Box 33)
- Letters/ Cards (Box 33)
- New York University (Box 33)
- The State of Tennessee (Box 33)
- Touchstone (Box 33)
- Magazine (Box 33)
- Network (Box 33)
- Dear Clara (Box 33)
- Saturday Review (Box 33)
- In Focus (Box 33)
- On Stage, October 1994 (Box 34)
- Metro government of Nashville (Box 34)
- Dialos (Box 34)
- Clara letters (Box 34)
- More letters (Box 34)
- Mrs. Clara (Box 34)
- Magazines and Nashville members (Box 34)
- Tennessee critic (Box 34)
- Clara articles 60 and 70s (Box 34)
- Premiere magazines (Box 34)
- Gannetteer (Box 34)
- Octogeranium Blooms (Box 34)
- Letter, Dear Clara (Box 34)
- Marked Copy (Box 34)
- Various Clara info (Box 35)
- Letters, University of South Alabama (Box 35)
- Clara in the Newspaper (Box 35)
- Always Patsy Cline (Box 35)
- Photos of Clara (Box 35)
- Dear Clara (Box 35)
- Programs (Box 35)
- Clara Hieronymous (Box 35)
- Nashville Children’s theatre (Box 35)
- Letters from interior design institute (Box 35)
- Shakespeare Association Of America (Box 35)
- Of trees and houses (Box 35)
- Las Casas- Paper Presentation (Box 36)
- Iberian Cultural Heritage (Box 36)
- Mexico’s Little Venice (Box 36)
- Photo and Magazines (Box 36)
- Population reference bureau, Inc. (Box 36)
- Paidea’s Amore (Box 36)
- Clara (Box 36)
- Clara’s got mail (Box 36)
- News of Clara (Box 36)
- Letters (Box 36)
- Tennessee’s art critic (Box 36)
- Accolade (Box 36)
- Award winning essay (Box 36)
- Plays (Box 36)
- Calling all stars (Box 36)
- TPAC Plays (Box 36)
- Clara Photos (Box 37)
- Clara Photos 2 (Box 37)
- Clara/ Requiem (Box 37)
- Various Clara (Box 37)
- Random Clara (Box 37)
- Washington Post (Box 37)
- More Post (Box 37)
- The Baccha Theatre Parthenon, 1990 (Box 37)
- Nashville, Here I am (Box 37)
- The Oresteia (Theatre) (Box 37)
- Plays (Box 37)
- The Bacchie (Translated by Anthony Lombardy) (Box 37)
- I never sang for my father by Robert Anderson (Box 37)
- If I live to see next fall (Box 37)
- In fashion (Box 37)
- We, the people (Box 37)
- Southern stage productions, INC (Box 37)
- Southern Baptist Conventions: A fundamental comedy by Frank Ash (Box 37)
- A house divided contact sheet (Box 37)